University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1962-1972
  - 1967-1968
    - To (Box 92:, Folder 1396)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 92:, Folder 1397)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (School of Social Work) (Box 92:, Folder 1398)
    - Trueheart, William (Box 92:, Folder 1399)
    - U (Box 92:, Folder 1400)
    - University Band (Box 92:, Folder 1401)
    - University Club (Box 92:, Folder 1402)
    - University Endowment Fund (Box 92:, Folder 1403)
    - University Foundation (Box 92:, Folder 1404)
    - University of Hawaii (Box 92:, Folder 1405)
    - University Scholars (Box 92:, Folder 1406)
    - University Secondary School (Box 92:, Folder 1407)
    - University Senate (Box 92:, Folder 1408)
    - University Security Police (Box 92:, Folder 1409)
    - Upward Bound (Box 92:, Folder 1410)
    - Urban League of Greater Hartford (Box 92:, Folder 1411)
    - Urban Schools Study (Box 92:, Folder 1412)
    - U.S. Dairy Association (Box 92:, Folder 1413)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 93:, Folder 1414)
    - Van Bibber, E. George (Box 93:, Folder 1415)
    - Veterinary Medicine (Box 93:, Folder 1416)
    - Vlandis, John (Director of Admissions) (Box 93:, Folder 1417)
    - Vouchers (Box 93:, Folder 1418)
    - W (Box 93:, Folder 1419)
    - Waller, William De Homer (Trustee) (Box 93:, Folder 1420)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 93:, Folder 1421)
    - West-end Project, Willimantic (Box 93:, Folder 1422)
    - Westledge School (Box 93:, Folder 1423)
    - Westover School (Box 93:, Folder 1424)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Dean, Graduate School) (Box 93:, Folder 1425)
    - WHUS (Box 93:, Folder 1426)
    - Wi (Box 93:, Folder 1427)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (Dean, Arts and Sciences) (Box 93:, Folder 1428)
    - X, Y (Box 93:, Folder 1429)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 93:, Folder 1430)
  - 1968-1969
    - A (Box 94:, Folder 1431)
    - AACTE Conference (Box 94:, Folder 1432)
    - Academy for Educational Development (Box 94:, Folder 1433)
    - Acknowledgements (Box 94:, Folder 1434)
    - Air Force (Box 94:, Folder 1435)
    - Alumni (Box 94:, Folder 1436)
    - Applications, letters from (Box 94:, Folder 1437)
    - Architects (Box 94:, Folder 1438)
    - Audio-Visual Center (Box 94:, Folder 1439)
    - Austin, Joseph - Comptroller (Box 94:, Folder 1440)
    - Austin School (Box 94:, Folder 1441)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 94:, Folder 1442-1444)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 95:, Folder 1445-1447)
    - Bailey, Clark L. (Box 95:, Folder 1448)
    - Bartlett Arboretum (Box 95:, Folder 1449)
    - Bequests (Box 95:, Folder 1450)
    - Benton, William (Box 95:, Folder 1451)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 95:, Folder 1452)
    - Blue Bikes (Box 95:, Folder 1453)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 95:, Folder 1454)
    - Braitmayer Foundation (Box 95:, Folder 1455)
    - Brooking Institute (Box 96:, Folder 1456)
    - Brotman, Michael (Box 96:, Folder 1457)
    - Buck, Ray (Publications) (Box 96:, Folder 1458)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 96:, Folder 1459)
    - Budget, State Department of (Box 96:, Folder 1460)
    - Budget, University (Box 96:, Folder 1461)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 96:, Folder 1462)
    - C (Box 96:, Folder 1463)
    - Carin Dinner 9/20 (Box 96:, Folder 1464)
    - Campus, Connecticut Daily (student newspaper) (Box 96:, Folder 1465)
    - Carnegie Foundation (Box 96:, Folder 1466)
    - Center for Black Studies (Box 96:, Folder 1467)
    - Center for Economic Education (Box 96:, Folder 1468)
    - Center for Italian Studies (Box 96:, Folder 1469)
    - Civil Defense (Box 96:, Folder 1470)
    - Cohen, Summer (Box 96:, Folder 1471)
    - Clark, Hugh (Box 96:, Folder 1472)
    - College Entrance Exam Board (Box 96:, Folder 1473-1474)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 97:, Folder 1475)
    - Commencement, Rosary Hill - cue sheet for H.D.B. (Box 97:, Folder 1476)
    - Commencement, Trinity College (Box 97:, Folder 1477)
    - Commencement, UConn (Box 97:, Folder 1478)
    - Commencement, Yale University (Box 97:, Folder 1479)
    - Commendations and Complaints (Box 97:, Folder 1480)
    - Commission on Aid to Higher Education (Box 97:, Folder 1481)
    - Commission for Higher Education (Box 97:, Folder 1482)
    - Committees
      - Bookstore Advisory (Box 97:, Folder 1483)
      - Advisory - Campus Security (Box 98:, Folder 1484)
      - Letters (Box 98:, Folder 1485)
      - Liaison - UConn, State Colleges and Community Colleges (Box 98:, Folder 1486)
      - Long-Range Planning ( Dorothy Goodwin) (Box 98:, Folder 1487)
      - Minutes (Box 98:, Folder 1488)
      - Racial Discrimination (Box 98:, Folder 1489)
      - Reports (Box 98:, Folder 1490)
    - Committees (Box 98:, Folder 1491)
      - Spiritual life of students (Box 98:, Folder 1492)
      - Traffic and Parking (Box 98:, Folder 1493)
    - Computer Center (Box 98:, Folder 1494)
    - Conferences (Box 98:, Folder 1495)
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station Board of Trustees (Box 98:, Folder 1496)
    - Connecticut Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 98:, Folder 1497)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 98:, Folder 1498)
    - Connecticut Development Commission (Box 98:, Folder 1499)
    - Connecticut Education Association (Box 98:, Folder 1500)
    - Connecticut Education Council ( H. Babbidge, Chairman) (Box 98:, Folder 1501)
    - Connecticut Educational TV (Box 98:, Folder 1502)
    - Connecticut Legislative Conference (Box 99:, Folder 1503)
    - CONNPEP (Box 99:, Folder 1504)
    - Connecticut Printers (Box 99:, Folder 1505)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (Box 99:, Folder 1506)
    - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 99:, Folder 1507)
    - Connecticut Science Fair (Box 99:, Folder 1508)
    - CONNTAC (Box 99:, Folder 1509)
    - Contracts (Box 99:, Folder 1510)
    - Council of Deans (Box 99:, Folder 1511)
    - Council on Instruction (Box 99:, Folder 1512)
    - Council of State Governments - Committee for Legislative Modernization (Box 99:, Folder 1513)
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 99:, Folder 1514)
    - CURE (Box 99:, Folder 1515)
    - D (Box 99:, Folder 1516)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 99:, Folder 1517)
    - Donahue, A. J. (Trustee) (Box 99:, Folder 1518)
    - E (Box 99:, Folder 1519)
    - Education Commission of the State (Box 99:, Folder 1520-1521)
    - Education Commission of the State (Box 100:, Folder 1522-1523)
    - Education, School of (Box 100:, Folder 1524)
    - Engineering, School of (Bronwell) (Box 100:, Folder 1525)
    - Enrollments (Box 100:, Folder 1526)
    - Evans, John M. (Vice President, Financial Affairs) (Box 100:, Folder 1527)
    - F (Box 100:, Folder 1528)
    - Faculty-Alumni Center (Box 100:, Folder 1529-1530)
    - Faculty Minutes (Box 101:, Folder 1531-1532)
    - Faculty Publications (Box 101:, Folder 1533)
    - Faculty Scholarships (Box 101:, Folder 1534)
    - Fees (Box 101:, Folder 1535)
    - Financial Aid ( J. W. Rapp) (Box 101:, Folder 1536)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 101:, Folder 1537)
    - Fingles, Franklin (Registrar) (Box 101:, Folder 1538)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 101:, Folder 1539)
    - Foreign Students (Box 102:, Folder 1540)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 102:, Folder 1541)
    - Freidman, Don (Box 102:, Folder 1542)
    - Fulbright Conference, 1969 June 15 - 19 (Box 102:, Folder 1543-1544)
    - Fuller, Alfred C., Trustee (Box 102:, Folder 1545)
    - G (Box 102:, Folder 1546)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Vice President for Academic Affairs, Provost) (Box 102:, Folder 1547)
    - Geographic Information System (Box 102:, Folder 1548)
    - Gr (Box 102:, Folder 1549)
    - Graduate School ( Nathan L. Whetten, Dean) (Box 102:, Folder 1550)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 102:, Folder 1551-1552)
    - H (Box 102:, Folder 1553)
    - Hansen, Henry (Box 102:, Folder 1554)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 103:, Folder 1555)
    - Hartford Hospital (Box 103:, Folder 1556)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 103:, Folder 1557)
    - Health Center (Box 103:, Folder 1558-1559)
    - Hewes, Robert E. (Dean of Students) (Box 103:, Folder 1560)
    - Hickey, James E. (Director of Athletics) (Box 103:, Folder 1561)
    - Holt, Guy B. (Trustee) (Box 103:, Folder 1562)
    - Home Economics, Department of (Box 103:, Folder 1563)
    - Honors Program (Box 103:, Folder 1564)
    - I (Box 103:, Folder 1565)
    - Inquiries (Box 103:, Folder 1566)
    - Institute of
      - International Education (Box 103:, Folder 1567)
      - International and Intercultural Studies (Box 103:, Folder 1568)
      - Living (Box 103:, Folder 1569)
      - Marine Biology (Rankin) (Box 104:, Folder 1570)
      - Marine Sciences (Peter Dehlinger, director) (Box 104:, Folder 1571)
      - Public Service (Box 104:, Folder 1572)
      - Material Science (Azaroff) (Box 104:, Folder 1573)
    - International Silver Award (Box 104:, Folder 1574)
    - Institute of Urban Research (Bosworth) (Box 104:, Folder 1575)
    - J (Box 104:, Folder 1576)
    - Joint projects office (Box 104:, Folder 1577)
    - K (Box 104:, Folder 1578)
    - Kammer, Harry (Box 104:, Folder 1579)
    - Kellogg Scholarships (Box 104:, Folder 1580)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 104:, Folder 1581)
    - Kersting, Edwin J. (Box 104:, Folder 1582)
    - L (Box 104:, Folder 1583)
    - Labor Education Center (Box 104:, Folder 1584)
    - Land-Grant (Box 104:, Folder 1585)
    - Land-Grant Committee, Student-Faculty Governance (Box 104:, Folder 1586)
    - Law School (Box 104:, Folder 1587)
    - Legislation - Federal (Box 104:, Folder 1588)
    - Legislation - State (Box 105:, Folder 1589-1590)
    - Library (Box 105:, Folder 1591)
    - Loeb Awards (Box 105:, Folder 1592)
    - M (Box 105:, Folder 1593)
    - Manning, Stuart (Box 105:, Folder 1594)
    - Manns, Curtis (Financial Aid Counselor) (Box 105:, Folder 1595)
    - McCormick, Joseph (Trustee) (Box 105:, Folder 1596)
    - McCullough, Don (Coordinator, Student Activities) (Box 105:, Folder 1597)
    - McMahon, Brien - Lecture Series (Box 105:, Folder 1598)
    - Museum of Art (Box 105:, Folder 1599)
    - Memberships (Box 105:, Folder 1600)
    - Museum (Box 105:, Folder 1601)
    - Mystic Seaport (Box 105:, Folder 1602)
    - N (Box 105:, Folder 1603)
    - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities (Box 105:, Folder 1604)
    - National Education Association (Box 106:, Folder 1605)
    - National School Service and Fund for Negro Students (Box 106:, Folder 1606)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 106:, Folder 1607)
    - Nature Conservancy L (Box 106:, Folder 1608)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 106:, Folder 1609)
    - New England Center for continuing Education (Box 106:, Folder 1610)
    - New England Council (Box 106:, Folder 1611)
    - New England Research Application Center (Box 106:, Folder 1612)
    - New positions (Box 106:, Folder 1613)
    - New England Presidents - Faculty Children Exchange Program (Box 106:, Folder 1614)
    - Nielsen, Carl (Trustee) (Box 106:, Folder 1615)
    - Noah Webster Foundation (Box 106:, Folder 1616)
    - Norris, Robert (Dean, Continuing Education) (Box 106:, Folder 1617)
    - Nursing, School of (Dean Gill) (Box 106:, Folder 1618)
    - O (Box 106:, Folder 1619)
    - Organization of Afro-American States (Box 106:, Folder 1620)
    - Old Sturbridge Village (Box 106:, Folder 1621)
    - Organization of Tropical Studies (Box 107:, Folder 1622)
    - Oriental Painter: 1-Hsiung Ju (Box 107:, Folder 1623)
    - P (Box 107:, Folder 1624)
    - Peace Corps (Box 107:, Folder 1625)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Harold and Career planning) (Box 107:, Folder 1626)
    - Presidential Scholar (Box 107:, Folder 1627)
    - President's Christmas card lists -, 1968 (Box 107:, Folder 1628)
    - President's Easter Egg Hunt (Box 107:, Folder 1629)
    - President's Lecture Series (Box 107:, Folder 1630)
    - President's Reception (Box 107:, Folder 1631)
    - President's Tea (Box 107:, Folder 1632)
    - Project Nehemiah (Box 107:, Folder 1633)
    - Project (Box 107:, Folder 1634)
    - Public Service Internships (Box 107:, Folder 1635)
    - Public Works Department (Box 107:, Folder 1636)
    - Questionnaires (Box 107:, Folder 1637)
    - R (Box 107:, Folder 1638)
    - Radio-TV Center (Box 108:, Folder 1639)
    - Rapp, John (Financial Aid Office) (Box 108:, Folder 1640)
    - Recommendation (Box 108:, Folder 1641)
    - Recruitment Policy (Box 108:, Folder 1642-1646)
    - Recruitment Policy (Box 109:, Folder 1647-1649)
    - Religious Education (Box 109:, Folder 1650)
    - Request for Literature, Catalogs, etc. (Box 109:, Folder 1651)
    - Research Council (Box 109:, Folder 1652)
    - Research Foundation (Box 109:, Folder 1653)
    - Research Grants (Box 109:, Folder 1654-1655)
    - Research Grants (Box 110:, Folder 1656)
    - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 110:, Folder 1657)
    - Rohrbach, John S. (Box 110:, Folder 1658)
    - ROTC (Box 110:, Folder 1659)
    - S (Box 110:, Folder 1660)
    - Sadik, Marvin (Museum of Art) (Box 110:, Folder 1661)
    - St. Francis Hospital (Box 110:, Folder 1662)
    - Salaries (Box 110:, Folder 1663)
    - SAND ( South Arsenal Neighborhood Development Corp.) (Box 110:, Folder 1664)
    - Selective Service (Box 110:, Folder 1665)
    - Semester on the 30s (Box 110:, Folder 1666)
    - Seven C's (Box 110:, Folder 1667)
    - Smith, E. O. School (Box 110:, Folder 1668)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 110:, Folder 1669)
    - Southeastern Branch (Box 110:, Folder 1670)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 110:, Folder 1671)
    - State College Presidents (Box 110:, Folder 1672)
    - State Health (Box 110:, Folder 1673)
    - State Highway (Box 110:, Folder 1674)
    - State Police (Box 111:, Folder 1675)
    - Sterling, M. Elizabeth (Box 111:, Folder 1676)
    - Student Senate (Box 111:, Folder 1677-1678)
    - Student Union (Box 111:, Folder 1679)
    - T (Box 111:, Folder 1680)
    - Tappan, Frances (Physical Therapy) (Box 111:, Folder 1681)
    - Tickets (Box 111:, Folder 1682)
    - Toner, John (Box 111:, Folder 1683)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 111:, Folder 1684)
    - Torrington Foundation for Public Giving (Box 111:, Folder 1685)
    - Trueheart, William (Box 111:, Folder 1686)
    - U (Box 111:, Folder 1687)
    - University Band (Box 111:, Folder 1688)
    - University Bookstore (Box 111:, Folder 1689)
    - University Foundation (Box 111:, Folder 1690)
    - University Honors Fellows (Box 111:, Folder 1691)
    - University Scholars (Box 111:, Folder 1692)
    - University Security (Box 111:, Folder 1693-1694)
    - Upward Bound (Box 112:, Folder 1695)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 112:, Folder 1696)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 112:, Folder 1697)
    - U.S. State Department (Box 112:, Folder 1698)
    - Urban Semester (Box 112:, Folder 1699)
    - V (Box 112:, Folder 1700)
    - Veterinary Medicine (Box 112:, Folder 1701)
    - Vlandis, John (Admissions) (Box 112:, Folder 1702)
    - Vouchers (Box 112:, Folder 1703)
    - W (Box 112:, Folder 1704)
    - Waller, William D. (Box 112:, Folder 1705)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 112:, Folder 1706)
    - WAYCAP (Box 113:, Folder 1707)
    - Westover School (Box 113:, Folder 1708)
    - WHUS (Box 113:, Folder 1709)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (Dean, Arts and Sciences) (Box 113:, Folder 1710)
    - X, Y (Box 113:, Folder 1711)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 113:, Folder 1712-1716)
    - Yale Committee - Nomination of Alumni Fellows (Box 113:, Folder 1717)
  - 1969-1970
    - A (Box 114:, Folder 1718)
    - Acknowledgements (Box 114:, Folder 1719)
    - Academy for Educational Development (Box 114:, Folder 1720-1721)
    - Advisors (Box 114:, Folder 1722)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center, James Lyons, Director (Box 114:, Folder 1723)
    - AID (Box 114:, Folder 1724)
    - Alcoa Foundation (Box 114:, Folder 1725)
    - Allied Health (Box 114:, Folder 1726)
    - Alumni (Box 114:, Folder 1727)
    - American Alumni Council - Grossigner's, New York (Box 114:, Folder 1728)
    - Architects (Box 114:, Folder 1729)
    - ASG ( Advisory Council of President) (Box 114:, Folder 1730)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 114:, Folder 1731)
    - B (Box 114:, Folder 1732)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 115:, Folder 1733-1742)
    - Bailey, Barbara (Trustee) (Box 116:, Folder 1743)
    - Barnard Fellows (Box 116:, Folder 1744)
    - Barlett Arboretum (Box 116:, Folder 1745)
    - Bequests (Box 116:, Folder 1746)
    - Benton, William (Box 116:, Folder 1747)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 116:, Folder 1748)
    - Black Personnel (Box 116:, Folder 1749)
    - Black Students (Box 116:, Folder 1750)
    - Board of Governors for Higher Education Centers (Box 116:, Folder 1751)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 116:, Folder 1752)
    - Braitmayer Foundation (Box 116:, Folder 1753)
    - Brotman, Michael (Auditorium) (Box 116:, Folder 1754)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 116:, Folder 1755)
    - Budget, University (Box 116:, Folder 1756)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 116:, Folder 1757)
    - C (Box 116:, Folder 1758)
    - Center for Black Studies (Box 116:, Folder 1759)
    - Center for Economic Education (Box 117:, Folder 1760)
    - Center for the Environment and Man, Inc. (Box 117:, Folder 1761)
    - Center for Italian Studies (Box 117:, Folder 1762)
    - Christmas Card lists -, 1969 (Box 117:, Folder 1763)
    - Christmas Party (Box 117:, Folder 1764)
    - Civil Defense (Box 117:, Folder 1765)
    - Clark, Hugh (Box 117:, Folder 1766)
    - Clippings (Box 117:, Folder 1767)
    - Cohen, Summer (Box 117:, Folder 1768)
    - College Bowl (Box 117:, Folder 1769)
    - College Entrance Exam Board (Box 117:, Folder 1770)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 117:, Folder 1771)
    - Commencement (Box 117:, Folder 1772)
    - Commencement (Box 118:, Folder 1773)
    - Commendation and Complaints (Box 118:, Folder 1774)
    - Commission on Aid to Higher Education (Box 118:, Folder 1775)
    - Commission for Higher Education, (2 folders) (Box 118:, Folder 1776)
    - Committee
      - Advisory - Athletics (Box 118:, Folder 1777)
      - Advisory - Bookstore (Box 118:, Folder 1778)
      - on Committees (Box 118:, Folder 1779)
      - Advisory - CONNPEP (Box 118:, Folder 1780)
      - Curricula and Courses (Box 118:, Folder 1781)
      - Financial Assistance Policy (Box 118:, Folder 1782)
      - for the Physically Handicapped Student (Box 118:, Folder 1783)
      - Health Services (Box 118:, Folder 1784)
      - Housing (Box 118:, Folder 1785)
      - Advisory - Inner College Experiment (Box 119:, Folder 1786)
      - Letters (Box 119:, Folder 1787)
      - Advisory - Library (Box 119:, Folder 1788)
      - Advisory - McCook Hospital (Box 119:, Folder 1789)
      - Minutes (Box 119:, Folder 1790)
      - Naming of Buildings (Box 119:, Folder 1791)
      - Nutritional Science in relation to foods and nutrition (Box 119:, Folder 1792)
      - Placement Policy (Box 119:, Folder 1793)
      - Long-range Planning (Box 119:, Folder 1794)
      - Pre-medical and Pre-dental (Box 119:, Folder 1795)
      - Advisory—Publications (Box 119:, Folder 1796)
      - Racial Discrimination (Box 119:, Folder 1797)
      - Radiological Safety (Box 119:, Folder 1798)
      - Reports (Box 119:, Folder 1799)
      - Advisory—ROTC (Box 119:, Folder 1800)
      - Advisory—Stamford Branch (Box 119:, Folder 1801)
      - Student-University relations (Box 119:, Folder 1802)
      - TAFS (Box 119:, Folder 1803)
      - Traffic and Parking (Box 119:, Folder 1804)
      - of Twenty (Box 119:, Folder 1805)
      - Liason— University of Connecticut, State Colleges and Community Colleges (Box 119:, Folder 1806)
      - on the use of Humans in Research (Box 119:, Folder 1807)
      - Community Service Proposals—Babbidge (Box 120:, Folder 1808-1811)
    - Community Development Action Plan (CDAP) (Box 120:, Folder 1812)
    - Computer Center (Box 120:, Folder 1813)
    - Conferences (Box 120:, Folder 1814)
    - Congressional Club— Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 120:, Folder 1815)
    - Connecticut Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 120:, Folder 1816)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 120:, Folder 1817)
    - Connecticut Daily Campus (student newspaper) (Box 120:, Folder 1818)
    - Connecticut Development Corporation (Box 120:, Folder 1819)
    - Connecticut Education Association (Box 121:, Folder 1820)
    - Connecticut Educational TV (Box 121:, Folder 1821)
    - Connecticut Health League (Box 121:, Folder 1822)
    - Connecticut Instructional TV (Box 121:, Folder 1823)
    - Connecticut Joint Council on Economic Education, Inc. (Box 121:, Folder 1824)
    - CONNPEP (Box 121:, Folder 1825)
    - Connecticut Printers (Box 121:, Folder 1826)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditures Council (Box 121:, Folder 1827)
    - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 121:, Folder 1828)
    - Connecticut Science Fair (Box 121:, Folder 1829)
    - CSEA awards for 25 years service (Box 121:, Folder 1830)
    - CONNTAC (Box 121:, Folder 1831)
    - Contracts (Box 121:, Folder 1832)
    - Connecticut Educational Council (Box 121:, Folder 1833)
    - Council of Deans (Box 121:, Folder 1834)
    - Council of State Governments, Committee on Legislative Modernization (Box 121:, Folder 1835)
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 121:, Folder 1836)
    - D (Box 121:, Folder 1837)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 121:, Folder 1838)
    - Day Care Center (Box 121:, Folder 1839)
    - Dean's Council (Box 121:, Folder 1840)
    - Debate Team (Box 121:, Folder 1841)
    - Donahue, A. J. (Trustee) (Box 121:, Folder 1842)
    - Drugs, Problem of (Box 121:, Folder 1843)
    - E (Box 121:, Folder 1844)
    - Earth Day (Box 122:, Folder 1845)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 122:, Folder 1846-1847)
    - Education, School of (Box 122:, Folder 1848)
    - Education, State Department (Box 122:, Folder 1849)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 122:, Folder 1850)
    - Enrollments (Box 122:, Folder 1851)
    - Evans, John M. (Vice President) (Box 122:, Folder 1852)
    - F (Box 122:, Folder 1853)
    - Faculty - Alumni Center (Box 122:, Folder 1854)
    - Faculty Minutes (Box 122:, Folder 1855)
    - Faculty Minutes (Box 123:, Folder 1856-1858)
    - Faculty Publications (Box 123:, Folder 1859)
    - Faculty Scholarships (Box 123:, Folder 1860)
    - Fairfield University (Box 123:, Folder 1861)
    - Fees (Box 123:, Folder 1862)
    - Financial Aid (Box 123:, Folder 1863)
    - >Finance and Control, State Department of (Box 123:, Folder 1864)
    - Fine Arts (Box 124:, Folder 1865)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 124:, Folder 1866)
    - Foreign Students (Box 124:, Folder 1867)
    - Friedman, Don (Box 124:, Folder 1868)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 124:, Folder 1869)
    - G (Box 124:, Folder 1870)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Box 124:, Folder 1871)
    - Gill, Joseph N. (Trustee) (Box 124:, Folder 1872)
    - (Box 124:, Folder 1873-1874)
    - Governor of Connecticut— John N. Dempsey (Box 124:, Folder 1875)
    - Governor's Environmental Policy Board (Box 124:, Folder 1876-1877)
    - Governor's Environmental Policy Board (Box 125:, Folder 1878)
    - Graduate School (Box 125:, Folder 1879)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 125:, Folder 1880)
    - Greater Hartford Council on Economic Education (Box 125:, Folder 1881)
    - H (Box 125:, Folder 1882)
    - Hansen, Henry—A. G. Extension (Box 125:, Folder 1883)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 125:, Folder 1884)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 125:, Folder 1885)
    - Health Center (Box 125:, Folder 1886-1887)
    - Health Center (Box 126:, Folder 1888)
    - Health Services (Box 126:, Folder 1889)